sourcevapes.com 2019-04-18

# Privacy Policy - SOURCEvapes

##### Last updated February 12th, 2015

Thank you for visiting the website of DC8 Distribution, Inc.’s SOURCEvapes® ("SOURCEvapes®" or “we”, “our”, or “us”). We recognize the importance of your privacy and are pleased to provide this privacy policy (the "Privacy Policy") to let you know how we collect and use information about visitors to our website with a homepage located at www.sourcevapes.com (the “website”).

### YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION  

Some sections of this website invite you to request publications and information about our products and merchandise, to place product orders or to contact us with comments and enquiries. In general, you do not have to provide personally identifiable information (“PII”) to use our website however if you do, so we will normally keep your email address and other details supplied by you on a database. We will not disclose any personal information you provide by means of this website to third parties unconnected with DC8 Distribution, Inc. without your consent, except to our data processors or as otherwise permitted by the relevant data protection legislation. Addresses, email addresses and other personal details supplied by means of this website will be used for the purposes for which you supply them or as stated on the relevant section of this website.

### COOKIES  

Like many websites, we may use "cookies" to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that we may transfer to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. We may use cookies to enable certain features of the website, to better understand how you interact with the website and to monitor aggregate usage by visitors and web traffic routing on the website. Affiliated third parties of SOURCEvapes® may place cookies on your browser for targeted advertising purposes. You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, our website’s customization features may not function, and/or you may not be able to use all portions of the website or all functionality of the website. 

### INFORMATION WE SHARE

SOURCEvapes® will not sell, share, or otherwise disclose any of the PII it collects through the website about you, except as described in this Privacy Policy or with your permission.

We may engage third party companies and individuals to perform services on our behalf, including without limitation, to facilitate our website, provide the website on our behalf, advertise the website and perform website-related services (e.g., without limitation, maintenance services, database management, web analytics and improvement of the website’s features) or to assist us in analyzing how our website is used. These third parties may have access to your PII. These service providers are not authorized by us to use or disclose the information except as necessary to perform services on our behalf, to comply with legal requirements or as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy.

We may engage affiliated third party companies to facilitate targeted advertising. Various forms of PII including IP addresses, cookie identifiers, and website activity may be collected for targeting advertising. These third parties will have access to such PII. Such PII may be used by third parties to target advertising on other sites based on your online activity.

From time to time, SOURCEvapes® may also co-sponsor programs or promotions, in which case SOURCEvapes® may share relevant PII (e.g., customer lists) for purposes of such program or promotion.

We may also disclose information about you that we have collected via the website to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including but not limited to subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of SOURCEvapes® or any third parties, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, illegal, unethical or legally actionable.

We reserve the right to transfer information we have about you and that we have collected via the website in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets. Should such a sale or transfer occur, we will use reasonable efforts to try to require that the transferee use PII you have provided through our website in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy.

### LINKS TO THIRD PARTY SITES

We may provide links to third-party websites that we do not control for your convenience and information. We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our website nor the information or content contained therein, or products or services that are offered through those sites. Please be aware that we are not and cannot be responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites and this Privacy Policy applies solely to information which we collect through our website.

SOURCEvapes® urges you to review the privacy policies posted on all websites at the time you first visit such websites. SOURCEvapes® cannot undertake any obligation to review or ensure enforcement or compliance with the privacy policy of any website to which we link.

### STORAGE AND TRANSFER OF DATA

We maintain administrative, technical, and physical safeguards for the website designed to protect against loss, misuse, or unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction of the PII we collect through the website.

Regardless of where you are located, SOURCEvapes®'s website collects information, and processes and stores that information in databases stored on servers located in the United States. 

### YOUR INFORMATION CHOICES

If you would like to update your contact information or preferences, or if you would like to have your information removed from our mailing list, please contact us by e-mailing us at support@SOURCEvapes.com.

Alternatively, when you receive certain electronic materials from us you may make use of any "opt out" provision in such communications so that we know that you no longer wish to receive such materials from us.

Further, you may opt out of having your PII used for targeting advertising by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance Consumer Choice opt-out site [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/) or the NAI opt-out site at [networkadvertising.org/choices](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/), or for those in Europe, the EDAA opt out site at [youronlinechoices.eu](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/).

To the extent required by law, we provide users with (i) reasonable access to the PII they provide through the website, and (ii) the ability to review, correct and delete such PII. To help protect your privacy, we take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access to your information.

### CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We will occasionally amend this Privacy Policy to reflect company, customer and other feedback. The effective date of the most recent Privacy Policy is noted at the top of this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to periodically review this policy to be informed of how we are committed to protecting your information and providing you with improved content on our Website. If we make any material changes in the way we collect, use, and/or share the personal information that you have voluntarily provided, we will notify you by posting notice of the changes in a clear and conspicuous manner on the SOURCEvapes® website. By using the [www.sourcevape.com](http://www.sourcevape.com/) site, you signify your agreement with the terms of this Privacy Policy.

### QUESTIONS ABOUT OUR PRIVACY POLICY AND CONTACTING SOURCEvapes®

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email at support@SOURCEvapes.com.

If you wish to discontinue or ‘opt out’ of the use of your personal data by SOURCEvapes®, or to unsubscribe from any newsletter or promotional materials, please contact us by email at support@SOURCEvapes.com.
